

### **NGUYEN VAN A**

#### **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

♥ Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and êm vào những câu hài hước hay thông tục). Nó để of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

#### **EDUCATION**



#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. as in administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult met, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magn and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to o pursue it, not even a lump. But as twho, as a goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working





Sep 2003 - 2007

#### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer he actual teachings of the great explorer of the t' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

## HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO

2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US với cá

#### **REFERENCES**



#### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

#### **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

### INTERESTS



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt you help trans and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities